Lecturer at a university
Then I consider to belong to a high resource authority
Class
And
The use of resources index is based on the existence
Different layers
People belong to different groups
Mountains in society
And Statistics Sweden then not me
Discarded by mapping
Conditions and
Low economic standard below
Three years
Or longer
Well then wins on
The head is close to social class and I must directly do listen some disappointed that there is none in
Unambiguous definition
Everyone can gather around
However, there are some things that most people agree
As namely that social class i deals with
Our financial factors
But also social background
Need each other
Now birth is just over but we'll look at the third and last concept
Withdrawal capital
Or more specifically symbolic
And it may well be defined as those that others think are important
Significant
So that which is a symbolic capital in a context it needs of course
Always be something
Think important or
Valuable
It is another context